Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Walt Horan Papers
1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Cage 192
Horan, Walter Franklin, 1898-1966.
270 Linear feet of shelf space 515 boxes Approximately 361,000 items
Walter Franklin Horan (1898-1966) was elected to the United States House of Representatives in 1942 as representative of the Fifth Congressional District of the State of Washington. The papers in this collection consist of correspondence to and from Walt Horan, interfiled and combined with other manuscripts and printed materials used in his official work.
Walter Franklin Horan (1898-1966) was elected to the United States House of Representatives in 1942 as representative of the Fifth Congressional District of the State of Washington. He served a total of eleven consecutive terms, from 1943 to 1964, losing the 1964 election to Thomas Foley. He was a member of several sub-committees of the House Appropriations Committee: Agriculture, Legislative, State, Commerce, Justice, and Judiciary, and served as Chairman of the District of Columbia Committee. Horan was a Republican.
Horan was born in Wenatchee, Washington, in 1898. He served in the United States Navy during World War I, and attended Washington State University, receiving his A.B. degree in 1925. He worked as an orchardist in Wenatchee.
The papers in this collection consist of correspondence to and from Walt Horan, interfiled and combined with other manuscripts and printed materials used in his official work. The consist of: government documents, when these were important to his work and to the file for reference and record; pamphlets and similar ephemeral materials, both solicited and unsolicited, issued by government agencies and corporate bodies and organizations; working papers and materials used in the legislative processes on the floor of the Congress and in hearings, including Mr. Horan’s recorded participation and his bills; records of services rendered constituents in their personal and official intercourse with the government, civil and military; communications with constituents through radio, television, and newsletter; and political materials of national, regional, and local concern, including biennial campaigns.
The original arrangement of materials has generally been preserved. Exceptions were made when the functions of an agency or bureau, for example, were modified, transferred, or ceased, or when a more comprehensive arrangement seemed desirable to bring all the papers having to do with same subject into closer proximity to simplify its use.
The outgoing office correspondence constitutes a name-index arranged alphabetically by years and will be useful in certain approaches to the papers. For example, a searcher wishing to examine the known correspondence of a Mr. Brown of Spokane may easily determine that Mr. Horan wrote to him on February 15, 1951, concerning the Rural Electrification Administration. Examination of the file of this agency will produce Mr. Brown’s letter of February 7, 1951, another copy of Mr. Horan’s reply, and attached will be any other correspondence Mr. Horan may have had with other persons or Government agencies in connection with his reply, along with a copy of any printed material which Mr. Horan sent to Mr. Brown.
Series 1: Personal Correspondence and Invitations, 1955-1961
Series 2: Outgoing Office Correspondence, 1943-1964
Series 3: Appropriations. Includes correspondence and supporting documentation:
Subseries 3.1: Appropriations, Agriculture; 1945-1964
Subseries 3.2: Appropriations, Army Civil Functions; 1948-1955
Subseries 3.3: Appropriations, Commerce, Justice, Judiciary, State; 1946-1962
Subseries 3.4: Appropriations, Interior; 1946-1964
Subseries 3.5: Appropriations, Legislative Branch and Public Works, 1949-1964
Series 4: Departmental, 1943-1964
Series 5: Subject files, 1943-1964
Series 6: Legislation, 1943-1964
Series 7: Communications with Constituents, 1945-1964
Series 8: Political, 1942-1964
Series 9: Extension 1, 1942-1951 (first addition to collection)
Series 10: Extension 2, 1943-1964 (second addition to collection)
Series 11: Oversize
This collection is open and available for research use.
The papers of Walter Franklin Horan, Representative in Congress from the 5th District of the State of Washington, were given to the Washington State University Library in 1964 by Mr. Horan. They were initially processed in July to November of 1965 by Earle Connette. Sally Horan donated additional papers in the late 1960s and early 1970s, and these were added to the collection. Between 2006 and 2011, the entire collection was comprehensively rehoused, and the descriptions in this collection guide were expanded to include information at the file level.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Horan, Walter Franklin, 1898-1966 -- Archives
United States. Congress. House.
United States -- Politics and government -- 1945-1989 -- Sources.
Legislators -- United States -- Correspondence.
Politics and Politicians; Washington (State)
- Series 1: Personal Correspondence and Invitations, 1955-1961
  - Personal Correspondence
    - January 1955-February 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - March 1955-May 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - June 1955-October 1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - November 1955-November 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - December 1956-March 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - April 1957-May 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - June 1957-August 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - September 1957-December 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Sally Horan: August 1944-July 1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Concerning Washington State University collection: January 1961-May 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Invitations
    - January 1955-February 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 20515 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - April 1956-May 1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - June 1956-August 1956 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - September 1956-December 1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - December 1956-January 1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - February 1957-March 1957 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 20911 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 20941 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - June 1957- July 1957 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - August 1957-October 1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - November 1957- December 1957 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Series 2: Outgoing Office Correspondence, 1943-1964
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1950
    - A- March-December 1943 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - A- January-June 1944 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - A- July 1944-March 1945 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - A- April-October 1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - A- November-December 1945 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - A- January-May 1946 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - A- June-December 1946 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - A- January-April 1947 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - A- May-December 1947 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - A- January-April 1948 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - A- May-December 1948 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - A- January-April 1949 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - A- May-December 1949 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - A- January-July 1950 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - A- August-December 1950 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - B- January-May 1943 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - B- June-September 1943 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - B- October-December 1943 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - B- January-February 1944 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - B- March-April 1944 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - B- May-August 1944 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - B- September-December 1944 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - B- January-February 1945 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - B- March-April 1945 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - B- May-June 1945 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - B- July-September 1945 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - B- October-November 15, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - B- November 16-December 1945 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - B- January-February 9, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - B- February 11-28, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - B- March 1946 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - B- April-May 16, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - B- May 18-June 1946 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - B- July-September 1946 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - B- October-December 1946 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - B- January-February 1947 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - B- March-April 1947 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - B- May-June 1947 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - B- July-September 1947 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - B- October-December 1947 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - B- January-February 1948 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - B- March 1948 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - B- April-May 1948 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - B- June-August 1948 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - B- September-December 1948 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - B- January-February 1949 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - B- March-April 1949 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - B- May-June 1949 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - B- July-August 1949 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - B- September-December 1949 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - B- January-February 1950 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - B- March-April 1950 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - B- May-June 1950 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - B- July-August 1950 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - B- September-October 1950 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - B- November 1950-January 1951 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - C- March-May 1943 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - C- June- September 1943 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - C- October-December 1943 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - C- January-March 1944 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - C- April-June 1944 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - C- July-December 1944 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - C- January-March 1945 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - C- April-May 1945 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - C- June-August 1945 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - C- September-October 1945 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - C- November-December 1945 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - C- January-February 1946 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - C- March 1946 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - C- April-May 23, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - C- May 24-July 1946 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - C- August-September 1946 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - C- November-December 1946 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - C- January-February 11, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - C- February 12-March 1947 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - C- April-May 1947 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - C- June-July 9, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - C- July 10-September 1947 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - C- October-December 1947 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - C- January-February 1948 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - C- March-April 10, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - C- April 13-June 1948 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - C- July-October 1948 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - C- November-December 1948 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - C- January-February 1949 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - C- March-April 11, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - C- April 12-May 1949 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - C- June-July 1949 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - C- August-October 1949 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - C- November-December 1949 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - C- January-March 7, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - C- March 8-April 1950 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - C- May-June 1950 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - C- July-August 1950 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - C- September-November 22, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - C- November 27-December 1950 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - D- January-June 1943 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - D- July-December 1943 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - D- January-April 1944 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - D- May-December 1944 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - D- January-April 1945 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - D- May-September 1945 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - D- October-December 1945 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - D- January-March 12, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - D- March 14-May 1946 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - D- June-August 1946 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - D- September-December 1946 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - D- January-February 1947 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - D- March-April 1947 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - D- May-July 1947 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - D- August-December 1947 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - D- January-March 16, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - D- March 17-May 1948 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - D- June-September 1948 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - D- October-December 1948 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - D- January-March 21, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - D- March 22nd-June 1949 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - D- July-December 1949 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - D- January-May 1950 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - D- June-September 8, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - D- September 12-December 1950 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - E- April 1943-March 1944 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - E- April 1944-June 1945 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - E- July-December 1945 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - E- January-April 1946 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - E- May-December 1946 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - E- January-April 1947 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - E- May-December 1947 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - E- January-April 1948 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - E- May-December 1948 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - E- January-May 1949 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - E- June 1949-February 1950 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - E- March-December 1950 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - F- March-July 1943 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - F- August-December 1943 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - F- January-April 1944 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - F- May-December 1944 (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - F- January-May 1945 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - F- June-October 1945 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - F- November 1945-February 13, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - F- February 14-May 13, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - F- May 14-August 1946 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - F- September-December 1946 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - F- January-February 1947 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - F- March-May 1947 (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - F- June-October 1947 (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - F- November 1947-February 1948 (Box 6, Folder 169)
    - F- March-April 1948 (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - F- May-December 1948 (Box 6, Folder 171)
    - F- January-April 1949 (Box 6, Folder 172)
    - F- May-December 13, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 173)
    - F- December 14, 1949-March 1950 (Box 6, Folder 174)
    - F- April-June 1950 (Box 6, Folder 175)
    - F- July-October 1950 (Box 6, Folder 176)
    - F- November-December 1950 (Box 6, Folder 177)
    - G- May-June 1943 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - G- July-November 1943 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - G- December 1943-April 1944 (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - G- May-November 1944 (Box 6, Folder 181)
    - G- December 1944-April 1945 (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - G- May-September 1945 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - G- October-December 1945 (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - G- January-March 21, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - G- March 25-June 1946 (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - G- July-October 14, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - G- October 15-November 1946 (Box 6, Folder 188)
    - G- December 1946-February 1947 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - G- March-April 1947 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - G- May-July 1947 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - G- August 1947-January 1948 (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - G- February-April 7, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - G- April 8-September 1948 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - G- October-December 1948 (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - G- January-March 1949 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - G- April-July 1949 (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - G- August-December 1949 (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - G- January-April 1950 (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - G- May-August 17, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - G- August 22-December 1950 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - H- March-May 8, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - H-May 10-July 5, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - H- July 6-September 1943 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - H- October-November 16, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - H- November 17-December 1943 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - H- January-February 1944 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - H- March-May 1944 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - H- June-August 1944 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - H- September-December 1944 (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - H- January-March 6, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - H- March 9-April 22, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 212)
    - H- April 23-June 1945 (Box 7, Folder 213)
    - H- July-September 1945 (Box 7, Folder 214)
    - H- October-November 10, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 215)
    - H- November 13-December 1945 (Box 7, Folder 216)
    - H- January-February 11, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 217)
    - H- February 12-March 5, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 218)
    - H- March 6-29, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 219)
    - H- April-May 21, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 220)
    - H- May 22-July 6, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 221)
    - H- July 9-August 1946 (Box 7, Folder 222)
    - H- September-October 1946 (Box 7, Folder 223)
    - H- November-December 1946 (Box 7, Folder 224)
    - H- January-February 12, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 225)
    - H- February 13-March 22, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 226)
    - H- March 24-April 1947 (Box 7, Folder 227)
    - H- May-June 6, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 228)
    - H- June 8-July 1947 (Box 7, Folder 229)
    - H- August-December 1947 (Box 7, Folder 230)
    - H- January-February 10, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 231)
    - H- February 11-March 11, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 232)
    - H- March 13-April 21, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 233)
    - H- April 22-May 1948 (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - H- June-July 1948 (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - H- August-October 23, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - H- October 26- December 1948 (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - H- January-February 16, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - H- February 17-March 22, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - H- March 23-May 5, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - H- May 10-July 1949 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - H- August-October 13, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - H- October 14-December 1949 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - H- January-March 6, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - H- March 7-April 18, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - H- April 20-June 1950 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - H- July 3-August 22, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - H- August 23-October 1950 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - H- November-December 1950 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - I- March 1943-December 1947 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - I- January 1948-December 1950 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - J- March 1943-December 1943 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - J- January-June 1944 (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - J- July 1944-April 1945 (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - J- May-December 1945 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - J- January-April 1946 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - J- May-August 1946 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - J- September-December 1946 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - J- January-April 1947 (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - J- May-December 1947 (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - J- January-May 1948 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - J- June-December 1948 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - J- January-April 1949 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - J- May-December 1949 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - J- January-July 1950 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - J- August-December 1950 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - K- March-December 1943 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - K- January-July 1944 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - K- August 1944-April 1945 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - K- May-October 1945 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - K- November 1945-February 14, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - K- February-April 1946 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - K- May-July 1946 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - K- August-December 1946 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - K- January-March 1947 (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - K- April-July 1947 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - K- August 1947-January 1948 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - K- February-April 12, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 278)
    - K- April 14-October 1948 (Box 8, Folder 279)
    - K- November 1948-March 9, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    - K- March 11-May 1949 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - K- June-August 1949 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - K- October 1949-February 1950 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    - K- March-July 1950 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - K- August-October 1950 (Box 8, Folder 285)
    - K- November-December 1950 (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - L- March-June 1943 (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - L- July-December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - L- January-May 1944 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - L- June-January 1945 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - L- February-May 1945 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - L- June-December 1945 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - L- January-May 16, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - L- March 21-June 1946 (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - L- July-December 1946 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - L- January-March 1947 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - L- April-July 10, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - L- July 11, 1947-January 20, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - L- January 21-April 8, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - L- April 10-July 9, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - L- July 23-December 1948 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - L- January-March 1949 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - L- April-June 1949 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - L- July-December 1949 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - L- January-March 1950 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - L- April-July 1950 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - L- August-October 1950 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - L- November-December 1950 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - M- January-May 15, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - M- May 17-September 1943 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - M- October-December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - M- January-March 8, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - M- March 11-June 16, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - M- June 17- November 1944 (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - M- December 1944-March 14, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - M- March 15-May 15, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - M- May 16-June 1945 (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - M- July-September 1945 (Box 8, Folder 318)
    - M- October-November 15, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - M- November 16-December 1945 (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - M- January-February 25, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - M- February 26-April 8, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - M- April 9- May 1946 (Box 8, Folder 323)
    - M- June-July 18, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 324)
    - M- July 20-October 9, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 325)
    - M- October 10-December 1946 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - M- January-February 13, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 327)
    - M- February 14-March 17, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 328)
    - M- March 18-April 23, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - M- April 24-June 9, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - M- June 11-July 22nd 1947 (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - M- July 23-November 1947 (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - M- December 1947-January 1948 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - M- February 1948 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - M- March-April 10, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - M- April 12-May 1948 (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - M- June-September 1948 (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - M- October-December 1948 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - M- January-February 15, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - M- February 16-March 1949 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - M- April-May 14, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 341)
    - M- May 16-July 12, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 342)
    - M- July 13-September 1949 (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - M- October-December 1949 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - M- January-February 23, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - M- February 24-April 17, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - M- April 18-June 1950 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - M- July-August 1950 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - M- September-October 1950 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - M- November-December 1950 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - N- April-March 1944 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - N- April 1944-February 1945 (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - N- March-October 1945 (Box 9, Folder 352)
    - N- November 1945-March 18, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 353)
    - N- March 20-December 1946 (Box 9, Folder 354)
    - N- January-June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - N- July 1947-February 1948 (Box 9, Folder 356)
    - N- March-December 1948 (Box 9, Folder 357)
    - N- January-June 1949 (Box 9, Folder 358)
    - N- July 1949-January 1950 (Box 9, Folder 359)
    - N- February-December 1950 (Box 9, Folder 360)
    - O- March-June 1944 (Box 9, Folder 361)
    - O- July-December 1944 (Box 9, Folder 362)
    - O- January 1945-July 1946 (Box 9, Folder 363)
    - O- August 1946-February 1947 (Box 9, Folder 364)
    - O- March-December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 365)
    - O- January-August 1948 (Box 9, Folder 366)
    - O- September 1948-June 1949 (Box 9, Folder 367)
    - O- July 1949-April 1950 (Box 9, Folder 368)
    - O- May-December 1950 (Box 9, Folder 369)
    - P- February-July 1943 (Box 9, Folder 370)
    - P- August-December 1943 (Box 9, Folder 371)
    - P- January-June 1944 (Box 9, Folder 372)